

ANUGNA SOUPATY

jnanu481@gmail.com | 6787560310 | Atlanta, Georgia

Summary

I am looking for a challenging environment where I can utilize my technical and analytical, theoretical skills as a (Designer). I have experience as a Clerk for three years. **Professional Experience Summary:** I Had Computer Knowledge and experience in multitasking. Till now fulfilled my dream working as a Teacher but now as my kids are grown up to go to elementary school I want to trun my career as a

Qualifications: Bachelor of Technology in Electronics and Communication Engineering. UX/UI Designer Boot Camp course in Georgia Technological University.

Technical Skills

- UX/UI Tools: Figma, Adobe XD, Miro, Google forms, Otter ai, Invision
- Web Browsers: Google Chrome, Mac Safari
- Application Technologies:
- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JAVA Scripts
- Research
- Front End Development
- UI Design
- Graphic Design
- Communication
- Taking User Interviews is one thing that I always eniov
- Designing Wireframes using Figma is my best
 skill
- Provide exemplary customer experience.
- collaborative

Projects

EASE car rental Mobile App(First Individual project)

HAP Event Mobile App(Group project of 4 people)

Redesign of Department of Treasury(DoT)(Group project of 4 people)

Redesign of a Non-profit website (Group project of 5 people)

Experience

Lead teacher

02/2022 - currently working

Working as a Lead teacher in Preschool at Goddard School, Woodstock, after acquiring **CDA** for preschool in February 2022.

Assistant teacher 09/2020 – 05/2021

Worked as Assistant teacher in Preschool at Primrose school of Harmony on the lakes,

Woodstock from September 2020 to June 2021.

Home Caregiver 07/2018 - 08/2019

Self | Atlanta, GA

Junior Assistant 03/2010 - 10/2013

12/2022

Andhra Pradesh Gov | Guntur, AP

Education and

raining Bachelor of Technology: Electronics And Communications Engineering 05/2010

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University | Andhra Pradesh, India

UX/UI Designer Boot Camp course in Georgia Technological University

(Certificate)

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/anugna-soupaty-643046148/

Hobbies Gardening, Cooking and Singing